[
  {
    "id": 254,
    "question": "How many points are there on the LU meridian?",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 255,
    "question": "Which of these movements is controlled by the Autonomic Nervous System?",
    "options": {
      "a": "pupil",
      "b": "finger",
      "c": "eye"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "eye"
  },
  {
    "id": 256,
    "question": "Lateral movement of the wrist when standing in anatomical position is called:",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Radial deviation"
  },
  {
    "id": 257,
    "question": "Which meridians are most involved in immunodeficiency disorders? energizer",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Lung and Triple"
  },
  {
    "id": 258,
    "question": "Myelinated fibers conduct impulses in which way? Salutatory (as opposed to continuos)",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 259,
    "question": "A term for one motor neuron and all the muscle fibers it innervates is:",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "A motor unit"
  },
  {
    "id": 260,
    "question": "Which are Adductors of the humerus?",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Pec Major and Lats"
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "question": "Flaccidity or flaccid muscle is due to which? Pathology or damage to anterior horn motor neuron (lower motor",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "..."
  },
  {
    "id": 262,
    "question": "What is the location of Ankylosing Spondylitis",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Vertebral column"
  },
  {
    "id": 263,
    "question": "The origin of Rectus Femoris is:",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "AIIS"
  }
]